# **MARIELLE**



# **ROBERTS**

FRONT-FND WFB DEVELOPER

## **PROFILE**

Roberts is an innovative and solution-driven developer who brings 10 years of progressive and professional experience; with a solid background in business development and intermittent coding experience, she has most recently completed a web development bootcamp. Roberts has transitioned her career and is seeking a front-end developer role. Seeking a remote opportunity in the United States or Canada that is the right fit.

# CONTACT



(647)291-7365



marielle@theredmoon.ca



marielle-roberts.com

## COURSES

**Immersive Web Development** Bootcamp - 2020 Juno College

Accelerated JavaScript - 2020 Juno College

Intro to Web Dev - 2020 Juno College



# SKILLS

**ASL** 

Early Adopter HTML5 CSS3 Data Management Javascript Critical Thinker Jauery **Excellent Communication** React Highly Collaborative **SEO** Strong Time Management **JSON** French REST API's Hebrew Accessibility Best German Practices Github Firebase Salesforce UX & UI Design ZenDesk



### **EXPERIENCE**

### Immersive Bootcamp • 2020

- Emphasis on: HTML5, CSS3, Responsive Design, jquery, Javascript, API's & React fundamentals
- Used REST API's and firebase for rich interactive development
- Excelled at pair programming and team collaboration
- Used version controls, wire-framing and created scope documents
- Regularly used Git and iTerm tools
- · Gained knowledge of web accessibility requirements
- Graduated with a personal portfolio of 6 web applications

# The Canadian National Institute for the Blind • Nov 2019 - Aug 2020

Development Officer/Major Gifts

Rondar Strategic Solutions Inc. • Nov 2018 - Nov 2019 Managing Consultant

Revolution Recycling & ITAD • Jul 2017 -Mar 2019

Business Development Manager

Further experience upon request.

# **EDUCATION**

Masters of Arts • 2014-2015

History/Semitic Languages York University

Hons. Bachelor of Arts • 2010-2014

York University